[CUT] Appears to be a transition or ending screen with limited content
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same content as previous
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same static content
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same content
[CUT] Redundant frame showing same view as previous
[CUT] Redundant frame showing same view
[CUT] Duplicate frame with no new information
[CUT] Returns to duplicate view with no new information
[CUT] Redundant view of earlier frame without new information
[CUT] Duplicate of previous frame with no new information
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same call screen
[CUT] Similar content to previous frame
[CUT] Redundant content
[CUT] Similar to earlier frames
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same content as earlier timestamp
[CUT] Duplicate of 27:30 frame showing same call interface
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same content as earlier timestamps
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same call interface as previous timestamps
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same content
[CUT] Duplicate frame with no new information
[CUT] No meaningful new content
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same content as previous
[CUT] Duplicate frame showing same content
[CUT] Shows meeting interface transition/setup screen
[CUT] Duplicate content from earlier frame
[CUT] Duplicate content from earlier frames